Browning W. Ware papers, Inclusive: 1928-2002, undated, Bulk: 1954-1988
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Audio Recordings, 1957-1962, undated; 6
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1982 April 18- 1982 July 25 (Box 59 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1982 August 1-1982 December 26 (Box 60 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1983 January 2-1983 April 17 (Box 61 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1983 April 24-1983 October 16 (Box 62 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1983 October 23-1984 April 1 (Box 63 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1984 April 8-1984 September 30 (Box 64 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1984 October 7-1985 March 31 (Box 65 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1985 April 7-1985 August 25 (Box 66 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1991 November 17-1992 May 31 (Box 67 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1992 June 7-1992 November 24 (Box 68 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1992 November 29-1993 May 17 (Box 69 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1993 May 23-1993 December 26 (Box 70 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1994 January 2-1994 July 31 (Box 71 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1994 August 7-1995 February 26 (Box 72 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1995 March 5-1995 June (Box 73 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 74 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 75 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 76 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 77 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 78 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 79 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1980-1989 (Box 80 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, 1989-1997 (Box 81 OVZ)
  - Cassette Tape Recordings, undated (Box 82 OVZ)